This file contains the data and analysis results, including code, for the group project in the Data Project course of the Cultural Data & AI master's program at the University of Amsterdam.
The data is divided into raw data and clean data.
	•	The raw data is stored in the file reddit_data.csv.
	•	The clean data is stored in the file reddit_clean_data.csv.
-----------------
The code has been saved in 
• Step_1_Data_mining.ipynb
• Step_2_Coherence_Score.ipynb,
• Step_3_Topic_Modeling_LDA_Mallet.ipynb,
• Step_4_graphs.ipynb
All the code is written in Python.
The code and data results are all stored in HTML format.
-----------------
WARNING:
• Due to the non-reproducibility of the LDA model, rerunning Topic_Modeling_LDA_Mallet.ipynb will retrain the model, which will result in differences between the newly generated analysis images and the original ones we used.
• If you want to retrain the LDA model, in addition to replacing the data input and output paths in the Topic_Modeling_LDA_Mallet.ipynb file, you also need to update the Mallet file path in the mallet_path function.
• The Mallet file path is located in the folder: ~/mallet-2.0.8/mallet-2.0.8/bin/mallet.
• If you only need to repeat the data results, you only need to replace the model input path and result output path.
• The model is stored in the PKL folder：dictionary.dict is the vocabulary collection generated during model training.
• lda_model is the model we used in this analysis
• ldamallet.pkl is a serialized (pickled) version of the trained LDA Mallet model which contains topic distributions, word-topic assignments, and all model parameters.
• The remaining folders and files contain results generated from partial executions, including PNG, HTML, and other formats.
